Love Always, Santa is a romance, comedy, tv movie
film directed by Brian Herzlinger.
After losing her husband Bradley three years ago on Christmas Day,
Celia Banks never thought she’d fall in love again.
Now, her entire world revolves around taking care of her daughter, Lilly.
Lilly writes a letter to Santa with one wish – for her
mommy to be happy and find love again.
Celia, played by Marguerite Moreau.
Jake, played by Mike Faiola.
Randy, played by Brady Smith.
Hank, played by Robert Jason Black.
Lily, played by Isadora Swann.
Bethany, played by Meghan Duffy.
Love Always, Santa is a 2016 romantic comedy television film
first broadcast by Hallmark Movies & Mysteries.
It was written by Brian Herzlinger and Jay Black, directed by
Herzlinger, and produced by MarVista Entertainment.
The film was set in and partially filmed in Northfield, Minnesota.
The film explores themes of holiday, anonymous letter, single
mother, ferris wheel, letter to santa claus.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.